You can now price gouge uber eats with claws.
Take two different phones.
Go to the same dish on uber.
Why are we getting different prices for the same food?
Look at this bro, it's a real thing.
We like price gouge uber back.
Sign up for this fish audio thing.
Connect it to your AI agent using their MCP.
Now clone your voice.
Just give this prop to go.
It'll show you how to do it.
Make sure to use their free pro model.
Create a table like this in whatever database you want.
Now we'll track restaurants you like.
And also create one for the dishes that you've ordered.
Get a free phone number from this VAPE thing.
Connect it to your fish audio voice.
Download these skills.
Mostly just this create call skill.
Now it's time to litter rip.
Want it looking at your previous dishes.
Researching similar restaurants that you would like.
And then ordering your food.
I straight up calling the restaurant using fish audio.
Trying to get the best price possible.
You do gotta pick up the food yourself though.
So, I would probably tell the agent how much you liked the dish.
So the system self improves on its own.
As a former AI dealer hater,
I can confidently say that fish audio
is the only one that doesn't sound like absolute cheek.
So go use it to price gouge Uber.
Follow your boy while you're at it.
Show you how to AI hack all this stuff for free.